Guide to the Asian CineVision Records TAM.416
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Asian CineVision Records
circa 1975-2014
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Asian CineVision (Organization)
Woo, John C.
TAM.416
314.25 Linear Feet in 313 record cartons, 1 legal manuscript box, 1 half manuscript box, 1 CD box, 1 poster tube, 1 oversize roll, and 1 oversize folder in a shared box.
6 websites in six archived websites.
Asian CineVision (ACV), founded by grassroots media activists in New York's Chinatown in 1976, is a non-profit media arts organization that develops, promotes and preserves media made by or about peoples of Asian descent. ACV initiated the weekly, cable-access Chinese Cable Television (CCTV), 1977-1983, which covered a broad range of community-interest issues such as local politics, education, language, housing, labor and healthcare. Beginning in 1978, ACV sponsored the Asian American International Film Festival (AIIFF). ACV also publishes the Asian American media arts journal CineVue. This unprocessed collection consists of three series: I, Administrative Files of Asian CineVision; II, Research Files; III, Video Recordings in various formats from Chinese Cable Television (CCTV), and the Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF).
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by John C. Woo on behalf of Asican CineVision, Inc. in 2007; additional materials were donated by the organization in 2011, 2013, 2017, and 2018. The accession numbers associated with this gift are 2008.007, 2008.008, NPA.2008.008, 2011.042, 2013.003, 2017.045, and 2018.135.
http://www.asiancinevision.org/ and http://aaiff.org/2014/ were initially selected by curators and captured through the use of The California Digital Library's Web Archiving Service in 2014 as part of the Arts and Cultural Left Web Archive. In 2015, these websites were migrated to Archive-It. Archive-It uses web crawling technology to capture websites at a scheduled time and displays only an archived copy, from the resulting WARC file, of the website. In 2018, http://aaiff.org/2018/ was added from a redirect of http://aaiff.org/. In 2019, http://aaiff.org/2015/, http://aaiff.org/2016/, and http://aaiff.org/2017/ were added. The accession number associated with these websites is 2019.125.
Arrangement
This unprocessed collection contains four series:
I. Administrative Files
II. Research Files
III. Video Recordings
IV. Addendum
V. Archived Websites
Historical Note
Asian CineVision (ACV) is a non-profit media arts organization that develops, promotes and preserves media made by or about peoples of Asian descent. Asian CineVision was founded by grassroots media activists in New York's Chinatown in 1976 to raise social and cultural awareness of the Asian American experience, both in the Asian American community and among the general public. Founders Tsui Hark, Christine Choy, Thomas Tam, Danny Yung and Peter Chow, and others also sought to raise awareness through media training in the local Chinese community. The organization sought to address problems of media access for Asian Americans and also to present and publicize the work of Asian American artists. The organization initiated the weekly, cable-access Chinese Cable Television (CCTV) in 1977, which covered a broad range of community-interest issues such as local politics, education, language, housing, labor and healthcare. Significantly, it was the first Chinese-language news program in the U.S. Production of CCTV ceased in 1983. Beginning in 1978, it has sponsored the Asian American (AIIFF) International Film Festival. In 1981, Asian CineVision assumed publication of Bridge magazine, a quarterly journal documenting the development of a pan-Asian American political and cultural identity previously published by the group Basement Workshop. Bridge ceased publication in 1986 and was replaced by the Asian American media arts journal CineVue. Through these and other programs, Asian CineVision supports Asian and Asian American mediamakers and presents their works to the Asian American community and wider audiences.
Custodial History
Asian CineVision, Inc. sent 238 boxes of records and graphics in 2007. Asian CineVision sent an additional 27 boxes of their records in 2011. In 2013, Asian CineVision sent an additional donation of 2 boxes containing posters, laptops and hard drives. In 2017 Asian CineVision sent three boxes of inventories and film festival programs.
Scope and Contents
This unprocessed collection consists of four series: I, Administrative Files of Asian CineVision (boxes 1-78, less the eleven interfiled boxes of series two); II, Research Files, i.e., background files on Asian American cinema, including a large collection of film catalogues (includes some notes in Chinese, and catalogs and magazines Spanish, Arabic, Korean, and Japanese (boxes 21-28, 40, 53, 67); III, Video Recordings (in various formats), from (A) Chinese Cable Television (CCTV), boxes 79-159, and (B) Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), i.e., motion pictures, short films, documentaries, and other video materials gathered in preparation for the festival (boxes 160-273); Addendum, 2011-2013 (unprocessed; boxes 274-300), which contains unidentified materials, posters, hard drives, and laptops.
Materials added to this collecion in 2017 include Programs from Asian American International Film Festivals (AAIFF) and Asian American International Video Festivals (AAIVF), dated 1978-2003. They also include inventories of Asian CineVision video archives, and catalog indexes of AAIFF programs and the Chinese-American cultural magazine Bridge.
Materials added to this collection in 2018 include programs from Asian American International Film Festivals (AAIFF) and Asian American International Video Festivals (AAIVF), copies of the periodical Cinevue, and office files related to these materials, dated 1976-2003.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Portions of this unprocessed collection are either in fragile condition, poorly housed, or loose. Therefore, in certain instances preservation concerns may take precedence, and, at the discretion of Library staff, some materials may not be available for use.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Born-digital materials have not been transferred and may not be available to researchers. Researchers may request access copies. To request that material be transferred, or if you are unsure if material has been transferred, please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Take Down Policy
Archived websites are made accessible for purposes of education and research. NYU Libraries have given attribution to rights holders when possible; however, due to the nature of archival collections, we are not always able to identify this information.
If you hold the rights to materials in our archived websites that are unattributed, please let us know so that we may maintain accurate information about these materials.
If you are a rights holder and are concerned that you have found material on this website for which you have not granted permission (or is not covered by a copyright exception under US copyright laws), you may request the removal of the material from our site by submitting a notice, with the elements described below, to the repository email.
Please include the following in your notice: Identification of the material that you believe to be infringing and information sufficient to permit us to locate the material; your contact information, such as an address, telephone number, and email address; a statement that you are the owner, or authorized to act on behalf of the owner, of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed and that you have a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; a statement that the information in the notification is accurate and made under penalty of perjury; and your physical or electronic signature. Upon receiving a notice that includes the details listed above, we will remove the allegedly infringing material from public view while we assess the issues identified in your notice.
Asian Americans in television broadcasting.; Asian American motion picture producers and directors.; Chinatown (New York, N.Y.); Asian Americans.; Asian American art -- Periodicals.; Asian American International Film Festival; Chinese Cable Television (New York, N.Y.).; Asian CineVision (Organization); Woo, John C.
- Series I: Administrative Files, 546092
  - ACV Grant applications, 1980-1990, bulk 1982-89; cuid2624; 546159 (Box 1)
  - TV Commercial, Inc., 1976-1995, bulk 1982-1983, 1994; cuid2625; 546158 (Box 2)
  - CCTV Production Workshop notes, 1976-1993; cuid2626; 546157 (Box 3)
  - Asian American Media Reference Guide, Asian American Media Reference Guide (2nd edition), CineVue Newsletter (2 sets), 1986-1995; cuid2627; 546156 (Box 4)
  - Bill Gee files, 1992-1996, bulk 1995-96; cuid2628; 546155 (Box 5)
  - Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF) Film Catalogues, 1978-87, 89-91, 94-96, 98, 2000); cuid2629; 546154 (Box 6, Box Shared Tamiment 065, Folder 3-4)
  - AAIFF 1978-1982 files, 1988 Press Release Promo Materials, 1978-1982, 1988 (bulk 1978-1982); cuid2630; 546153 (Box 7)
  - AAIFF #6-8, 1983-1985; cuid2631; 546152 (Box 8)
  - AAIFF #8-9, 1985-1986; cuid2632; 546151 (Box 9)
  - AAIFF #10-12, Videoscape (1992-1993), 1987-1989, 1992-1993; cuid2633; 546150 (Box 10)
  - AAIFF #12, 1989; cuid2634; 546149 (Box 11)
  - AAIFF #14, 1991; cuid2635; 546148 (Box 12)
  - AAIFF #14-15, 1991-1992; cuid2636; 546147 (Box 13)
  - AAIFF #14-15, 1991-1992; cuid2637; 546146 (Box 14)
  - AAIFF #15-16, 1992-1993; cuid2638; 546145 (Box 15)
  - AAIFF #16, Videoscape 1992, 1992-1993; cuid2639; 546144 (Box 16)
  - AAIFF files #16-18 (1993-1995), Videoscape 1992, Children's Film Series 1994-1995, 1992-1995; cuid2640; 546143 (Box 17)
  - AAIFF #16-17, 20, 1993-1994, 1997; cuid2641; 546142 (Box 18)
  - AAIFF #20, 1997; cuid2642; 546141 (Box 19)
  - AAIFF #18,22, 1995, 1999; cuid2643; 546140 (Box 20)
  - 14th and 15 AAIFF World Tour press clips and programs, 1991-1992; cuid2644; 546139 (Box 29)
  - CineVue Newsletter notes (Vol. IX No. 2, Vol. IX No. 3, Vol. X No. 1), 15th Film Fest Files (Asian American International Video Festival 1986), 1988-1990 "Talk 'N' Cheap" series (with individuals such as Jessica Hagedorn, David Henry Hwang, Bi-lingual poe, 1986-1992; cuid2645; 546138 (Box 30)
  - CineVue Newsletter notes (Vol. 1 No. 1, Vol. 1 No. 3, Vol. 1 No. 4, Vol. 2 No. 1, Vol. 2 No. 4, Vol. 1 No. 5, Vol. 3 No. 1, Vol. 3 No. 2, Vol. 3 No. 3, Vol. 4 No. 1, Vol. 4 No. 2, Vol. 4 No.3), 1986-1989; cuid2646; 546137 (Box 31)
  - Film Festival Files (including Asian American International Video Festival and Children's Film Series), 1988-1990; cuid2647; 546136 (Box 32)
  - Videoscape 1993 and 1994 Files, 1993-1994; cuid2648; 546135 (Box 33)
  - 1995 film submission for Videoscape, 3-ring binder with articles about various films (arranged alphabetically by film name), "Angels!" on unknown media format, 1995-2000 (bulk 1995); cuid2649; 546134 (Box 34)
  - 1978-1991 AAIFF catalogues, 2 copies of each except 1988 and 1990, cuid2650; 546133 (Box 35)
  - Film Festival Shorts entries, 2000; cuid2651; 546132 (Box 36)
  - AAIFF Press clips (articles about AAIFF), 1991-1997; cuid2652; 546131 (Box 37)
  - AAIFF Tours (1996, 1997, 1998), 19th AAIFF film files, 1996-1998; cuid2653; 546130 (Box 38)
  - 2001 Sponsor information, 1999 and 2000 Film festival logistics files, 1997 and 1998 film festival files, and filmmaker files, 1992-2001; cuid2654; 546129 (Box 39)
  - AAIFF logistics files 1987 and 1988, 1997 AAIFF tour, posters, invitations, etc., 1987-1997; cuid2655; 546128 (Box 41)
  - Film photo stills, cuid2656; 546127 (Box 42)
  - ACV AAIFF logistics (tour and press), 1996-1992; cuid2657; 546126 (Box 43)
  - AAIFF 1988 logistics, other film festival catalogues, 1988-1997; cuid2658; 546125 (Box 44)
  - AAIFF 1997 film files, cuid2659; 546124 (Box 45)
  - ACV grant applications, circa 1990s; cuid2660; 546123 (Box 46)
  - ACV corporate sponsors, other film festival catalogues and programs, circa 1990s; cuid2661; 546122 (Box 47)
  - Films (stills, flyers, articles), CCTV production notes, 1995; cuid2662; 546121 (Box 48)
  - AAIFF (1997-1998) film files, 1996-1998; cuid2663; 546120 (Box 49)
  - Media catalogues, circa 1980s; cuid2664; 546119 (Box 50)
  - Bridge (magazine) Files, circa early-mid 1980s; cuid2665; 546118 (Box 51)
  - Funding/Grant applications, including Apple, NYCH, NEH, and CPB, 1975-1998 (bulk 1975-1986); cuid2666; 546117 (Box 52)
  - AAIFF, 2001, film files, cuid2667; 546116 (Box 54)
  - AAIFF, 2001, film files, corporate sponsors for AAIFF (1996), 1996-2001; cuid2668; 546115 (Box 55)
  - Children's Film Series, Videoscape files, and Asian American Media Resource Guide entries (2 binders), 1985-1991; cuid2669; 546114 (Box 56)
  - Asian Film Series (1988-1989), Chinese Film Series (1990), 1988-1990; cuid2670; 546113 (Box 57)
  - AAIFF (1990-1991) film files, cuid2671; 546112 (Box 58)
  - Staff meeting notes, Radio Drama and Production Workshop, and James Wong Howe clippings, 1975-1995; cuid2672; 546111 (Box 59)
  - Screenplay contest, including entries for The Motel and Saving Face, 2001; cuid2673; 546110 (Box 60)
  - ABC Talent Scholarship Grant Program applications, including applications from Greg Pak and Julie Cho, 2000-2001; cuid2674; 546109 (Box 61)
  - Corporate sponsors for AAIFF (1996), cuid2675; 546108 (Box 62)
  - AAIFF (1995, 1998) film files, cuid2676; 546107 (Box 63)
  - AAIFF (1998) submissions, filmmaker files, cuid2677; 546106 (Box 64)
  - AAIFF (1990, 1993) submissions, cuid2678; 546105 (Box 65)
  - Cinema and Society, AAIFF (1990, 1995, 1996) logistic files, 1989-1996; cuid2679; 546104 (Box 66)
  - Other Asian American organization event flyers, brochures, circa 1990s; cuid2680; 546103 (Box 68)
  - Other Asian American organizations event flyers, brochures, circa 1990s; cuid2681; 546102 (Box 69)
  - Other Asian American organization newsletters/information, circa 1990s; cuid2682; 546101 (Box 70)
  - CineVue (1997), Bridge (1984-1985), Asian New Yorker (1997), AAIFF film files (1995), 1984-1997; cuid2683; 546100 (Box 71)
  - CCTV files, 1976-1978; cuid2684; 546099 (Box 72, Box MSOS007, Folder 1)
  - AAIFF film catalogues, AAIVF film catalogues, ACV publications (including Bridge, CineVue, and 1976 perspective), 1976-2000; cuid2685; 546098 (Box 73, Box MSOS007, Folder 2)
  - ACV flyers, posters, and invitations to ACV events including AAIFF and Videoscape, circa 1980-1990s; cuid2686; 546097 (Box 74)
  - G-P Film Reviews, circa 1995-1998; cuid2687; 546096 (Box 75)
  - Photographs of CCTV, AAIFF, and other ACV events, circa late 1970s-1990s; cuid2688; 546095 (Box 76)
  - Large-sized contact sheets and long prints of film posters., cuid2689; 546094 (Box 77)
  - New York State Council on the Arts (NYCA) grant files, including proposals for writer-in- residence programs for Joyce Howe and Luis H. Francia., 1984-1990; cuid2690; 546093 (Box 78)
  - Programs: Asian American International Film Festival, 1978-2003; cuid2709 (Box 311, Box 312)
  - Programs: Asian American International Video Festival, 1982-1988, 1990; cuid2710 (Box 312)
  - Programs, Publications, and Flyers: Assorted, circa 1975-1995; cuid2711 (Box 311)
  - Inventories and Catalog Indexes, 2002-2006; cuid2712 (Box 312)
  - Festival Programs, Publications, and Office Files, 1976-2003 (Box 314, Box 315)
- Series II: Research Files, 546080
  - ACV Research Files on Nuclear Disarmament and Hiroshima Survivors, cuid2691; 546091 (Box 21)
  - Film Distribution Companies A-F, cuid2692; 546090 (Box 22)
  - Film Distribution Companies S-W, 1988-1997; cuid2693; 546089 (Box 23)
  - Agency A-C, cuid2694; 546088 (Box 24)
  - Agency N-Z, cuid2695; 546087 (Box 25)
  - Film Festival Catalogues, cuid2696; 546086 (Box 26)
  - Film Festival Catalogues, cuid2697; 546085 (Box 27)
  - ACV Research Magazines/Serials, cuid2698; 546084 (Box 28)
  - Social Issues: article clippings, newspapers and newsletters on issues including Japanese internment, Japanese redress and reparation, East Coast Asian Student Union, Housing Problem, and Pan Asian American Women's group, c. early 1980s; cuid2699; 546083 (Box 40)
  - Agency D-N files, cuid2700; 546082 (Box 53)
  - Film Distribution companies I-P, cuid2701; 546081 (Box 67)
- Series III: Video Recordings, 545120
  - Video 001: CCTV Jul 1976 ACV Preview, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1631; 546079 (Box 79)
  - Video 002: CCTV Aug 15, 1976/Aug 26, 1976 Broadcast tape News, Social Service Program, Tuberculosis, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1632; 546078 (Box 79)
  - Video 003: CCTV Aug 15, 1976/Aug 22, 1976 Broadcast tape Cultural festival, New Year show, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1633; 546077 (Box 79)
  - Video 004: CCTV Aug 22, 1976/Aug 26, 1976 Broadcast tape News, Drama "The World of Ah Sing," Living in Chinatown, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1634; 546076 (Box 79)
  - Video 005: CCTV Aug 22, 1976/Aug 26, 1976 Broadcast tape Special report: Singing contest, Asian American Experience, A Grain of Sand, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1635; 546075 (Box 79)
  - Video 006: CCTV Aug 29, 1976/Sep 2, 1976 Broadcast tape News, Social Service Program, Mental health, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1636; 546074 (Box 79)
  - Video 007: CCTV Aug 29, 1976/Sep 2, 1976 Broadcast tape Profile: Yu Li Wah, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1637; 546073 (Box 79)
  - Video 008: CCTV Sep 5, 1976/Sep 9, 1976 Broadcast tape News, Drama "The World of Ah Sing", Housewife, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1638; 546072 (Box 79)
  - Video 009: CCTV Sep 5, 1976/Sep 9, 1976 Broadcast tape Cultural festival, variety show, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1639; 546071 (Box 79)
  - Video 010: CCTV Sep 12, 1976/Sep 16, 1976 Broadcast tape News, Social Service Program, Youth Program, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1640; 546070 (Box 79)
  - Video 011: CCTV Sep 12, 1976/Sep 16, 1976 Broadcast tape Drama "The World of Ah Sing", Job hunting, Asian American Experience: Racism in Comic books, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1641; 546069 (Box 79)
  - Video 012: CCTV Sep 19, 1976/Sep 23, 1976 Broadcast tape News, Special Report: Buddhism in Chinatown, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1642; 546068 (Box 79)
  - Video 013: CCTV Sep 19, 1976/Sep 23, 1976 Broadcast tape Profile: His Yang, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1643; 546067 (Box 79)
  - Video 014: CCTV Sep 26, 1976/Sep 30, 1976 Broadcast tape News, Social Service Program, Banking, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1644; 546066 (Box 79)
  - Video 015: CCTV Sep 26, 1976/Sep 30, 1976 Broadcast tape Cultural Festival (CPC Cultural Festival I), Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1645; 546065 (Box 79)
  - Video 016: CCTV Oct 3, 1976/Oct 7, 1976 Broadcast tape News, Drama "The World of Ah Sing," Getting Sick, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1646; 546064 (Box 79)
  - Video 017: CCTV Oct 3, 1976/Oct 7, 1976 Broadcast tape Profile: Han Shang Niu, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1647; 546063 (Box 79)
  - Video 018: CCTV Oct 10, 1976/Oct 16, 1976 Broadcast tape News, Social Service Program, Manpower training, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1648; 546062 (Box 79)
  - Video 019: CCTV Oct 10, 1976/Oct 16, 1976 Broadcast tape Special Report: Chinese American relationship, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1649; 546061 (Box 79)
  - Video 020: CCTV Oct 14, 1976/Oct 18, 1976 Broadcast tape, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1650; 546060 (Box 79)
  - Video 021: CCTV Oct 17, 1976/Oct 21, 1976 Broadcast tape News, Social Service Program, Senior Citizen Service, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1651; 546059 (Box 79)
  - Video 022: CCTV Oct 17, 1976/Oct 21, 1976 Broadcast tape Cultural Festival (CPC Cultural Festival II), Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1652; 546058 (Box 79)
  - Video 023: CCTV Oct 24, 1976/Oct 28, 1976 Broadcast tape News, Social Service Program, Checkup, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1653; 546057 (Box 79)
  - Video 024: CCTV Oct 24, 1976/Oct 28, 1976 Broadcast tape Profile: Mrs. Lee of Mahusua restaurant, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1654; 546056 (Box 79)
  - Video 025: CCTV Oct 31, 1976/Nov 4, 1976 Broadcast tape News, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1655; 546055 (Box 79)
  - Video 026: CCTV Nov 7, 1976/Nov 11, 1976 Broadcast tape, Jul 1976-Jan 23, 1977; cuid1656; 546054 (Box 79)
  - Video 027: CCTV Nov 21, 1976/Nov 25, 1976 Broadcast tape News, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1657; 546053 (Box 80)
  - Video 028: CCTV Nov 28, 1976/Dec 2, 1976 Broadcast tape News, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1658; 546052 (Box 80)
  - Video 029: CCTV Dec 5, 1976/Dec 9, 1976 Broadcast tape News, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1659; 546051 (Box 80)
  - Video 030: CCTV Dec 12, 1976/Dec 16, 1976 Broadcast tape News, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1660; 546050 (Box 80)
  - Video 031: CCTV Dec 18, 1976/Dec 22, 1976 Broadcast tape, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1661; 546049 (Box 80)
  - Video 032: CCTV Dec 26, 1976/Dec 30, 1976 Broadcast tape News, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1662; 546048 (Box 80)
  - Video 033: CCTV Jan 2, 1977/Jan 6, 1977 Broadcast tape News, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1663; 546047 (Box 80)
  - Video 034: CCTV Jan 9, 1977/Jan 13, 1977 Broadcast tape News, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1664; 546046 (Box 80)
  - Video 035: CCTV Jan 16, 1977 Broadcast tape News, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1665; 546045 (Box 80)
  - Video 036: CCTV Jan 23, 1977 Broadcast tape News, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1666; 546044 (Box 80)
  - Video 037: CCTV Jan 30, 1977 Broadcast tape News, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1667; 546043 (Box 80)
  - Video 038: CCTV Feb 27, 1977 Broadcast tape News, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1668; 546042 (Box 80)
  - Video 039: CCTV Feb 27, 1977 Broadcast tape Special Report: Peking Opera, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1669; 546041 (Box 80)
  - Video 040: CCTV Mar 6, 1977 Broadcast tape News, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1670; 546040 (Box 80)
  - Video 041: CCTV Mar 13, 1977 Broadcast tape News, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1671; 546039 (Box 80)
  - Video 042: CCTV Mar 13, 1977 Broadcast tape, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1672; 546038 (Box 80)
  - Video 043: CCTV Mar 20, 1977 Broadcast tape News, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1673; 546037 (Box 80)
  - Video 044: CCTV Mar 20, 1977 Broadcast tape, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1674; 546036 (Box 80)
  - Video 045: CCTV Mar 27, 1977 Broadcast tape News, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1675; 546035 (Box 80)
  - Video 046: CCTV Mar 27, 1977 Broadcast tape, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1676; 546034 (Box 80)
  - Video 047: CCTV Apr 3, 1977 Broadcast tape News, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1677; 546033 (Box 80)
  - Video 048: CCTV Apr 10, 1977 Broadcast tape News, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1678; 546032 (Box 80)
  - Video 049: CCTV Apr 17, 1977 Broadcast tape News, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1679; 546031 (Box 80)